{"metadata":{"generator":"Captivate","generatorVersion":"10.0.1","schemaVersion":"","author":"author","title":"","description":"project description","email":"author@company.com","website":"www.company.com","tags":"","thumbnail":"","source":"assets","durationInFrames":1500,"frameRate":30,"totalSlides":11,"width":640,"height":480,"responsive":false,"scalable":true,"launchFile":"index.html"},"contentStructure":[{"id":"Text_Caption_331","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_331","title":"Information Security Awareness Quiz --Security While Travelling-- ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_574","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_574","title":"Take our Security Quiz   to test your knowledge.    Click on Begin to start. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_575","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_575","title":"Brought to you by the Information Security Branch  Office of the Chief Information Officer ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Button_9","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_9","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si21887","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si21901","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Slide21706","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_331","Text_Caption_574","Text_Caption_575","Button_9","si21887","si21901"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide21706"}}},{"id":"Image_189","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_189","roles":{}},{"id":"si12441","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_338","roles":{}},{"id":"si12349","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_327","title":"1.  According to research, a laptop is stolen every 53 seconds.  To protect yours while traveling by vehicle, is it best practice to lock it out of sight in the trunk of your vehicle? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12360","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_328","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12364","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_329","title":"Yes. The laptop would be secure out of sight in the trunk. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12360_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"175","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Yes. The laptop would be secure out of sight in the trunk.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si12382","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_332","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12386","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_333","title":"No. The trunk is not secure. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12382_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"179","roles":{"answer":{"title":"No. The trunk is not secure.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si12435","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_337","roles":{}},{"id":"si12459","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_42","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12473","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_43","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19347","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19361","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19593","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19606","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19621","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19634","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19649","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19662","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19677","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19690","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12405","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_334","title":"Correct - Answer:  B  It is surprising how many computers have been stolen from locked trunks.  Even without seeing someone store their device, a Wi-Fi signal can be detected from inside a trunk before the device enters sleep mode (which can be up to 30 minutes). Cars with trunk release buttons are targets for thieves to break the window to release and many trunks can be pried open with a crow bar. It is best practice to keep your device with you when possible.   Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12417","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_335","title":"Incorrect  - Answer:  B  It is surprising how many computers have been stolen from locked trunks.  Even without seeing someone store their device, a Wi-Fi signal can be detected from inside a trunk before the device enters sleep mode (which can be up to 30 minutes). Cars with trunk release buttons are targets for thieves to break the window to release and many trunks can be pried open with a crow bar. It is best practice to keep your device with you when possible.   Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12429","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_336","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide12483","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_189","si12349","si12364","si12386","si12459","si12473","si19347","si19361","si19593","si19606","si19621","si19634","si19649","si19662","si19677","si19690","si12429"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide12483"},"question":{"interactionId":"12329","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"1.  According to research, a laptop is stolen every 53 seconds.  To protect yours while traveling by vehicle, is it best practice to lock it out of sight in the trunk of your vehicle?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_190","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_190","roles":{}},{"id":"si22070","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_714","roles":{}},{"id":"si21978","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_698","title":"2. When preparing your computer for travel, you should: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21989","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_704","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21993","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_705","title":"Ensure you are running the latest version of your Operating System ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21989_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"175_394","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Ensure you are running the latest version of your Operating System\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si22000","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_706","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22004","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_707","title":"Set your computer to lock the screen after a short period of time  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22000_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"179_395","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Set your computer to lock the screen after a short period of time \r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si24737","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24741","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Ensure your device is password-protected with a strong password ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24737_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Ensure your device is password-protected with a strong password\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si24752","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24756","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back up your files before leaving home  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24752_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Back up your files before leaving home \r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si24848","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24852","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"All of the above ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24848_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"All of the above\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si22064","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_713","roles":{}},{"id":"si22092","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_103","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide22259q1","for":"Slide22259q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22110","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_104","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide22259q1","for":"Slide22259q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22132","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_105","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide22259q1","for":"Slide22259q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22150","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_106","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide22259q1","for":"Slide22259q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22162","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide22259q1","for":"Slide22259q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22174","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide22259q1","for":"Slide22259q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22186","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide22259q1","for":"Slide22259q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22198","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide22259q1","for":"Slide22259q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22210","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide22259q1","for":"Slide22259q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22222","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide22259q1","for":"Slide22259q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22234","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide22259q1","for":"Slide22259q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22246","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide22259q1","for":"Slide22259q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22034","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_710","title":"Correct - Answer:  E  While it may be annoying to keep entering your password to unlock your computer, it is best to ensure it locks so no one can access it in your absence. Strengthen your security by downloading the most current Operating System and patches and ensure you back up your files before you leave.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22046","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_711","title":"Incorrect  - Answer:  E  While it may be annoying to keep entering your password to unlock your computer, it is best to ensure it locks so no one can access it in your absence. Strengthen your security by downloading the most current Operating System and patches and ensure you back up your files before you leave.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22058","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_712","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide22259","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_190","si21978","si21993","si22004","si24741","si24756","si24852","si22092","si22110","si22132","si22150","si22162","si22174","si22186","si22198","si22210","si22222","si22234","si22246","si22058"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide22259"},"question":{"interactionId":"21958","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"2. When preparing your computer for travel, you should:\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["E"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_191","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_191","roles":{}},{"id":"si22393","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_725","roles":{}},{"id":"si22301","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_699","title":"3. When using public Wi-Fi (check all that apply):  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22312","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_715","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22316","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_716","title":"Choose the ‘Public Network’ setting to configure your computer for greater security  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22316","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide22582q2"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si22312_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Choose the ‘Public Network’ setting to configure your computer for greater security \r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si22323","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_717","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22327","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_718","title":"Use a VPN (Virtual Private Network) to encrypt your communication  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22327","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide22582q2"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si22323_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Use a VPN (Virtual Private Network) to encrypt your communication \r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si22334","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_719","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22338","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_720","title":"Ensure your ‘file sharing’ setting is off. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22338","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide22582q2"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si22334_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Ensure your ‘file sharing’ setting is off.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si24863","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24867","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Only use a password-protected Wi-Fi to ensure it is secure ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24867","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide22582q2"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si24863_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Only use a password-protected Wi-Fi to ensure it is secure\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si22387","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_724","roles":{}},{"id":"si22415","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_107","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide22582q2","for":"Slide22582q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22433","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_108","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide22582q2","for":"Slide22582q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22455","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_109","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide22582q2","for":"Slide22582q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22473","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_110","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide22582q2","for":"Slide22582q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22485","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide22582q2","for":"Slide22582q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22497","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide22582q2","for":"Slide22582q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22509","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide22582q2","for":"Slide22582q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22521","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide22582q2","for":"Slide22582q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22533","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide22582q2","for":"Slide22582q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22545","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide22582q2","for":"Slide22582q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22557","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide22582q2","for":"Slide22582q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22569","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide22582q2","for":"Slide22582q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22357","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_721","title":"Correct - Answer:  A,B,C  If you are given a choice, the ‘Public Network’ option considers you will be exposed to public Wi-Fi and locks down certain security options. There are reputable VPN services available for $2-$3 per month, well worth the investment. Do a search on your computer for your operating system's name to turn off “file sharing\". Be aware that even password-protected Wi-Fi spots are not totally secure and check that the URL you are connected to is the exact address of the Wi-Fi home page.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22369","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_722","title":"Incorrect  - Answer:  A,B,C  If you are given a choice, the ‘Public Network’ option considers you will be exposed to public Wi-Fi and locks down certain security options. There are reputable VPN services available for $2-$3 per month, well worth the investment. Do a search on your computer for your operating system's name to turn off “file sharing\". Be aware that even password-protected Wi-Fi spots are not totally secure and check that the URL you are connected to is the exact address of the Wi-Fi home page.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22381","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_723","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24883","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Partial Correct - Answer:  A,B,C  If you are given a choice, the ‘Public Network’ option considers you will be exposed to public Wi-Fi and locks down certain security options. There are reputable VPN services available for $2-$3 per month, well worth the investment. Do a search on your computer for your operating system's name to turn off “file sharing\". Be aware that even password-protected Wi-Fi spots are not totally secure and check that the URL you are connected to is the exact address of the Wi-Fi home page.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide22582","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_191","si22301","si22316","si22327","si22338","si24867","si22415","si22433","si22455","si22473","si22485","si22497","si22509","si22521","si22533","si22545","si22557","si22569","si22381"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide22582"},"question":{"interactionId":"22281","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"3. When using public Wi-Fi (check all that apply): \r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A","B","C"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_192","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_192","roles":{}},{"id":"si22716","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_736","roles":{}},{"id":"si22624","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_700","title":"4. Using a Public Computer is perfectly safe if you are using it to check Google maps, museum hours, or public transit schedules.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22635","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_726","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22639","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_727","title":"True ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22635_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"True\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si22646","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_728","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22650","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_729","title":"False ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22646_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"False\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si22710","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_735","roles":{}},{"id":"si22738","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_111","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide22905q3","for":"Slide22905q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22756","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_112","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide22905q3","for":"Slide22905q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22778","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_113","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide22905q3","for":"Slide22905q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22796","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_114","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide22905q3","for":"Slide22905q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22808","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide22905q3","for":"Slide22905q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22820","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide22905q3","for":"Slide22905q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22832","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide22905q3","for":"Slide22905q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22844","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide22905q3","for":"Slide22905q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22856","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide22905q3","for":"Slide22905q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22868","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide22905q3","for":"Slide22905q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22880","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide22905q3","for":"Slide22905q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22892","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide22905q3","for":"Slide22905q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22680","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_732","title":"Correct - Answer:  A  Accessing public information not connected to an account or personal information is totally safe on a public computer.  The danger lies in malware that has already infected the computer recording everything you type such as log-in information and passwords. Make sure you unclick any ‘stay signed in’ or ‘remember me’ boxes and it’s a good idea to delete history or cookies when you’re done with your session.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22692","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_733","title":"Incorrect  - Answer:  A  Accessing public information not connected to an account or personal information is totally safe on a public computer.  The danger lies in malware that has already infected the computer recording everything you type such as log-in information and passwords. Make sure you unclick any ‘stay signed in’ or ‘remember me’ boxes and it’s a good idea to delete history or cookies when you’re done with your session.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22704","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_734","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide22905","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_192","si22624","si22639","si22650","si22738","si22756","si22778","si22796","si22808","si22820","si22832","si22844","si22856","si22868","si22880","si22892","si22704"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide22905"},"question":{"interactionId":"22604","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"4. Using a Public Computer is perfectly safe if you are using it to check Google maps, museum hours, or public transit schedules. \r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_193","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_193","roles":{}},{"id":"si23144","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_749","roles":{}},{"id":"si23041","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_701","title":"5.  When using your phone away from home: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23052","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_737","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23056","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_738","title":"It is safe to access your financial information, it has strong protection ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23052_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"175_403","roles":{"answer":{"title":"It is safe to access your financial information, it has strong protection\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si23063","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_739","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23067","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_740","title":"It doesn’t matter if you use Wi-Fi or cellular service, security is the same ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23063_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"179_404","roles":{"answer":{"title":"It doesn’t matter if you use Wi-Fi or cellular service, security is the same\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si23074","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_741","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23078","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_742","title":"Turn on your locator service so your family will know where you are if you get lost ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23074_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"399_405","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Turn on your locator service so your family will know where you are if you get lost\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si23085","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_743","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23089","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_744","title":"Public charging stations are not only convenient but safe to use ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23085_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"406","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Public charging stations are not only convenient but safe to use\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si24894","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24898","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"None of the above ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24894_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"None of the above\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si23138","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_748","roles":{}},{"id":"si23166","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_115","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide23333q4","for":"Slide23333q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23184","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_116","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide23333q4","for":"Slide23333q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23206","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_117","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide23333q4","for":"Slide23333q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23224","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_118","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide23333q4","for":"Slide23333q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23236","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide23333q4","for":"Slide23333q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23248","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide23333q4","for":"Slide23333q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23260","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide23333q4","for":"Slide23333q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23272","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide23333q4","for":"Slide23333q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23284","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide23333q4","for":"Slide23333q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23296","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide23333q4","for":"Slide23333q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23308","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide23333q4","for":"Slide23333q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23320","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide23333q4","for":"Slide23333q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23108","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_745","title":"Correct - Answer:  E  Think of your phone as another computer where Wi-Fi signals can be intercepted and your input  clearly seen.  It is slightly more secure to use the cellular service over Wi-Fi and it is best to turn off your phone’s location tracking so no one knows you are not at home; GPS information is embedded in your pictures, consider saving your vacation photos to send once you are home. Also keep in mind that malware can be hidden in a USB connector, whether purchased new or publicly used to re-charge your phone.   Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23120","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_746","title":"Incorrect  - Answer:  E  Think of your phone as another computer where Wi-Fi signals can be intercepted and your input  clearly seen.  It is slightly more secure to use the cellular service over Wi-Fi and it is best to turn off your phone’s location tracking so no one knows you are not at home; GPS information is embedded in your pictures, consider saving your vacation photos to send once you are home. Also keep in mind that malware can be hidden in a USB connector, whether purchased new or publicly used to re-charge your phone.   Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23132","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_747","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide23333","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_193","si23041","si23056","si23067","si23078","si23089","si24898","si23166","si23184","si23206","si23224","si23236","si23248","si23260","si23272","si23284","si23296","si23308","si23320","si23132"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide23333"},"question":{"interactionId":"23021","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"5.  When using your phone away from home:\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["E"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_194","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_194","roles":{}},{"id":"si23482","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_763","roles":{}},{"id":"si23379","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_750","title":"6.  It’s a good idea to follow the directions from the ‘find my phone’ app if your phone is stolen.   ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23390","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_751","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23394","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_752","title":"True ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23390_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"175_407","roles":{"answer":{"title":"True\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si23401","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_753","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23405","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_754","title":"False ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23401_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"179_408","roles":{"answer":{"title":"False\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si23476","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_762","roles":{}},{"id":"si23504","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_119","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23522","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_120","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23544","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_121","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23562","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_122","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23574","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23586","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23598","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23610","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23622","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23634","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23646","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23658","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23446","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_759","title":"Correct - Answer:  B  If you are fairly certain that the phone was stolen, it is best to let the authorities (police/security) follow-up as you do not know who you may encounter when attempting to retrieve it. If it was your Government device that was stolen, ensure you report it to 1-866-660-0811 and follow the incident reporting process: http://www2.gov.bc.ca/gov/content/governments/services-for-government/information-management-technology/information-security/information-incidents  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23458","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_760","title":"Incorrect  - Answer:  B  If you are fairly certain that the phone was stolen, it is best to let the authorities (police/security) follow-up as you do not know who you may encounter when attempting to retrieve it. If it was your Government device that was stolen, ensure you report it to 1-866-660-0811 and follow the incident reporting process: http://www2.gov.bc.ca/gov/content/governments/services-for-government/information-management-technology/information-security/information-incidents  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23470","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_761","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide23671","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_194","si23379","si23394","si23405","si23504","si23522","si23544","si23562","si23574","si23586","si23598","si23610","si23622","si23634","si23646","si23658","si23470"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide23671"},"question":{"interactionId":"23359","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"6.  It’s a good idea to follow the directions from the ‘find my phone’ app if your phone is stolen.\r\r\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_195","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_195","roles":{}},{"id":"si23820","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_777","roles":{}},{"id":"si23717","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_764","title":"7.  There is always a risk that your device will be confiscated when passing through an international border.  The best insurance to keep your information safe would be (click all that apply): ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23728","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_765","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23732","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_766","title":"Leave your device at home ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23732","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide24009q6"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si23728_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Leave your device at home\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si23739","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_767","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23743","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_768","title":"Hide your device so the border agents cannot see it ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23743","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide24009q6"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si23739_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Hide your device so the border agents cannot see it\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si23750","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_769","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23754","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_770","title":"Back up your information and delete all confidential information ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23754","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide24009q6"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si23750_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Back up your information and delete all confidential information\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si24909","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24913","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Acquire a ‘burner phone’ and SIM card to use in the visiting country  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24913","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide24009q6"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si24909_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Acquire a ‘burner phone’ and SIM card to use in the visiting country \r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si24924","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24928","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Contact your supervisor and see if you qualify for a travel loaner device ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24928","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide24009q6"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si24924_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Contact your supervisor and see if you qualify for a travel loaner device\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si23814","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_776","roles":{}},{"id":"si23842","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_123","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23860","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_124","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23882","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_125","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23900","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_126","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23912","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23924","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23936","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23948","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23960","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23972","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23984","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23996","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23784","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_773","title":"Correct - Answer:  A,C,D,E  Never hide your device as you are required by law to submit it for inspection and be aware that your checked baggage is scanned and searched as well. It is the employee’s responsibility to know the travel policy before leaving the country, please review our travel policy here:  http://gww.fin.gov.bc.ca/gws/pt/rmb/ref/gsoOutofCountryTravelSecurityPolicy.pdf  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23796","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_774","title":"Incorrect  - Answer:  A,C,D,E  Never hide your device as you are required by law to submit it for inspection and be aware that your checked baggage is scanned and searched as well. It is the employee’s responsibility to know the travel policy before leaving the country, please review our travel policy here:  http://gww.fin.gov.bc.ca/gws/pt/rmb/ref/gsoOutofCountryTravelSecurityPolicy.pdf  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23808","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_775","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24947","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Partial Correct - Answer:  A,C,D,E  Never hide your device as you are required by law to submit it for inspection and be aware that your checked baggage is scanned and searched as well. It is the employee’s responsibility to know the travel policy before leaving the country, please review our travel policy here:  http://gww.fin.gov.bc.ca/gws/pt/rmb/ref/gsoOutofCountryTravelSecurityPolicy.pdf  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide24009","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_195","si23717","si23732","si23743","si23754","si24913","si24928","si23842","si23860","si23882","si23900","si23912","si23924","si23936","si23948","si23960","si23972","si23984","si23996","si23808"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide24009"},"question":{"interactionId":"23697","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"7.  The annual Smarter Cities IT market opportunity is expected to be __ Billion?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A","C","D","E"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_196","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_196","roles":{}},{"id":"si24158","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_791","roles":{}},{"id":"si24055","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_778","title":"8. What is the highest priority when you are traveling internationally: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24066","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_779","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24070","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_780","title":"Security of confidential information ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24066_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"175_415","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Security of confidential information\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si24077","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_781","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24081","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_782","title":"Security of devices ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24077_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"179_416","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Security of devices\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si24958","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24962","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Personal safety and security ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24958_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Personal safety and security\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si24973","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24977","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Proper behaviour and adherence to visiting country’s laws ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24973_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Proper behaviour and adherence to visiting country’s laws\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si24152","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_790","roles":{}},{"id":"si24180","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_127","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide24347q7","for":"Slide24347q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24198","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_128","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide24347q7","for":"Slide24347q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24220","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_129","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide24347q7","for":"Slide24347q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24238","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_130","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide24347q7","for":"Slide24347q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24250","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide24347q7","for":"Slide24347q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24262","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide24347q7","for":"Slide24347q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24274","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide24347q7","for":"Slide24347q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24286","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide24347q7","for":"Slide24347q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24298","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide24347q7","for":"Slide24347q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24310","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide24347q7","for":"Slide24347q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24322","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide24347q7","for":"Slide24347q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24334","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide24347q7","for":"Slide24347q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24122","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_787","title":"Correct - Answer:  C  The number one priority is always your personal safety. Be aware of your surroundings, know where your emergency exits are in transit and where you can get assistance on the ground. You are your most valuable asset.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24134","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_788","title":"Correct - Answer:  C  The number one priority is always your personal safety. Be aware of your surroundings, know where your emergency exits are in transit and where you can get assistance on the ground. You are your most valuable asset.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24146","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_789","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide24347","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_196","si24055","si24070","si24081","si24962","si24977","si24180","si24198","si24220","si24238","si24250","si24262","si24274","si24286","si24298","si24310","si24322","si24334","si24146"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide24347"},"question":{"interactionId":"24035","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"8. What is the highest priority when you are traveling internationally:\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["C"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_185","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_185","roles":{}},{"id":"Text_Caption_107","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_107","title":"Quiz Results ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6059","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si6083","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si6091","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si6055","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You Scored: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6079","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Total Questions: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6087","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Accuracy: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6103","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si6107","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"continue","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6121","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Review Quiz ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"review","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20489","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"continue","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20502","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"continue","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20517","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Review Quiz ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"review","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20530","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Review Quiz ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"review","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide6038","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide6038"}}},{"id":"si6231","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_186","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_186","roles":{}},{"id":"Button_4","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_4","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si19054","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si19068","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_9","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_9","title":" Stay Current With Information Security By Subscribing to the:   Weekly Security News Digest ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_298","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_298","title":"Thank you for taking the quiz.  To exit the quiz, close the browser window. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide6219","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si6231","Image_186","Button_4","si19054","si19068","SmartShape_9","Text_Caption_298"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":600},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide6219"}}},{"id":"Pool502","class":"pool","roles":{"pool":{"id":502,"name":"Pool1","questions":[]}}},{"id":"August2019Quiz","class":"project","title":"August2019Quiz","children":["Slide21706","Slide12483","Slide22259","Slide22582","Slide22905","Slide23333","Slide23671","Slide24009","Slide24347","Slide6038","Slide6219"],"roles":{"quiz":{"id":458,"branched":false,"submitAll":false,"review":true,"questions":["Slide12483q0","Slide22259q1","Slide22582q2","Slide22905q3","Slide23333q4","Slide23671q5","Slide24009q6","Slide24347q7"],"minScore":0,"maxScore":80,"passScore":64}}}],"contentSettings":{"global":{"branchAware":false},"toc":{"enabled":false},"playbar":{"enabled":true,"cc":false,"playPause":true,"back":true,"forward":true,"rewind":true,"close":true,"mute":true,"progressBar":true}},"contentReporting":{"CCCriteria":"quiz","CCData":{"quizData":"quiz_passed"},"SCCriteria":"quiz","SCData":{"quizData":"quiz_passed"},"exitNormalIfCompleted":false},"toc":[{"id":"Slide21706","title":"Slide 1"},{"id":"Slide12483","title":"Slide 2"},{"id":"Slide22259","title":"Slide 3"},{"id":"Slide22582","title":"Slide 4"},{"id":"Slide22905","title":"Slide 5"},{"id":"Slide23333","title":"Slide 6"},{"id":"Slide23671","title":"Slide 7"},{"id":"Slide24009","title":"Slide 8"},{"id":"Slide24347","title":"Slide 9"},{"id":"Slide6038","title":"Slide 10"},{"id":"Slide6219","title":"Slide 11"}]}